I may not have a real on my account
but i have a story
and i will show you
my plan on how to get rich with her
here or
everything we profited from in these thirty days
we donated one hundred percent yesterday on that social project
only this time the legacy will continue
Fabius told me
that the crybaby was a very funny guy
and this is the stop that I was reflecting
I thought bro
Charlie Brown cannot be a brand that
arrives at one and does not arrive at the other
our brand has to be chosen too
is on
gotta get it to the whole world brother
and it was with that in mind that I created 1 idea
ah it's nice eh
well the season has come to an end
but the brand continues
Charlie Brown Junior
the news is that now we will make it
take him to your house door bro
that's right
it's not just in Santos now
it's for all of Brazil
now you will order and it will arrive at your house
the link is in the bio
now
you can have the skate wheel shaped brownie
directly there throughout Brazil
anywhere
Charlie Brown and Santos Junior
for all of Brazil boy worth
thank you brother
tamo together
caraca worth
come on bora bora
hour cannon
your place bro
look there
haha